pressking.com 2013-12-18

# Privacy Policy - PressKing

## 1\. Information we collect and how we use it

In order to provide our full range of Services, we may collect the following types of information:

**Information you provide** – When you sign up for a PressKing account, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address, an account password, or credit card or other payment account information), which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers.

**Cookies** – When you use the Services, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results, and tracking user trends.

**Log information** – When you access the Services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

**User communications** – When you send email or other communications to PressKing, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

**Links** – PressKing may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology and customized content.

**Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to PressKing Services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or the links from within our Services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

PressKing only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our Services, including the display of customized content

  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services

  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network

  * Protecting the rights or property of PressKing or our users

  * Developing new services

PressKing processes personal information on our servers in France and in other countries. In some cases, we may process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own Services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party.

## 2\. Choices for personal information

When you sign up for the Services, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features or Services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our Services, in which case PressKing may not be able to provide those Services to you.

## 3\. Information sharing

PressKing only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of PressKing in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information

  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures

  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of PressKing, its users or the public as required or permitted by law

If PressKing becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular hyperlink. Such information does not identify you individually.

## 4\. Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.

We restrict access to personal information to PressKing employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are also bound by confidentiality obligations.

## 5\. Data integrity

PressKing processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy.

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

## 6\. Accessing and updating personal information

When you use PressKing services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at any time, if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.

## 7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

PressKing reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Updated versions of the Privacy Policy will be made available on or through the Services and will have immediate effect. Continued use of the Services after any such changes constitutes your consent to such changes.

“PressKing” is owned and operated by PressKing SAS, 17 Square Edouard VII, 75009 Paris, France.
